Inventory of the Chinese Cultural Revolution collection
Hoover Institution Archives
Chinese Cultural Revolution collection
1966-1976
2007C53
Hoover Institution Archives
6 manuscript boxes, 15 oversize boxes (6.8 linear feet)
Newspaper issues, pamphlets, broadsides, flyers, and sound recordings, issued by Red Guards, relating to the Chinese Cultural Revolution.
Access
Collection is open for research.
Use copies of some sound recordings in this collection are available for immediate access. To listen to other sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2007, with increments received in 2015 and 2017.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Scope and Content of Collection
Newspaper issues, pamphlets, broadsides, flyers, and sound recordings, issued by Red Guards, relating to the Chinese Cultural Revolution.
An increment received in 2015 contains documents relating to revolutionary activities in the Beijing and Shanghai areas and Mao Zedong’s directives to party members and the Red Guards against his political rivals, notably the former chairman of the People’s Republic, Liu Shaoqi, and Liu’s wife, Wang Guangmei.
China--History--Cultural Revolution, 1966-1976.; Sound recordings.
- Newspapers, 1966-1976 (Boxes 1-14)
  - An hui ba er qi 安徽八.二七 [合肥], 安徽省合肥工人革命造反派联合委员会, 安徽省八. 二七革命造反兵团, 1967 December (Box-folder 1: 1)
  - Ba ba zhan bao 八八战报 北京, 中央民族歌舞团八.八革命造反者毛泽东思想红卫兵, 1967 February-August (Box-folder 1: 2)
  - Ba er liu jing lei 八.二六惊雷 [N.p.], 贫下中农灌县革命造反司令部, 东方红八.二六战斗团灌县分团, 1967 August 28 (Box-folder 1: 3)
  - Ba er liu pao sheng 八.二六炮声 [N.p.], 四川大学东方红8.26战斗团, 红卫兵川大支队, 红代会中国科技大学东方红公社, 中国科学院 红卫兵革命造反司令部, 1967 June 1, December 18 (Box-folder 1: 4)
  - Ba er qi zhan bao 八.二七战报 [南京], 南京大学八.二七革命串联会宣传组, 1966 December; 1967 January-November; 1968 February-March (Box-folder 1: 5)
  - Ba er si 八二四 [开封], 开封师范学院八二四革命造反委员会, 1967 August 4 (Box-folder 1: 6)
  - Ba san zhan bao 八三战报 [南京], 南京东方红大学八三革命造反师, 1967 March-July, October (Box-folder 1: 7)
  - Ba shu feng huo 巴蜀烽火 [N.p.], 成都工人革命造反兵团江电纵队巴蜀烽火, 天津一机筹委海河评论, 天津一教联委编辑部, 1967 September 17, November (Box-folder 1: 8)
  - Ba yi ba zhan bao 八一八战报 [N.p.], 青海省八一八革命造反派红卫兵代表大会, 1967 September 20 (Box-folder 1: 9)
  - Ba yi ba zhan bao 八一八战报 [N.p.], 红代会河北大学毛泽东思想 “八.一八”红卫兵 “八一八”战报编辑部, 1967 May 10, July 1 (Box-folder 1: 10)
  - Ba yi san hong wei bing 八.一三红卫兵 [天津], 天津大学八.一三红卫兵报编辑部, 1967 April 30, June 14, July 18 (Box-folder 1: 11)
  - Ba yi san hong wei bing 八.一三红卫兵 [天津], 天津大学八.一三红卫兵批判刘, 邓, 陶联络站赴保调查组, 1967 April (Box-folder 1: 12)
  - Ba yi wu zhan bao 8.15 战报 [重庆], 重庆红卫兵革命造反司令部, 重庆大学红卫兵, 八.一五战斗团, 1967 March 3 (Box-folder 1: 13)
  - Ba yi zhan bao 八一战报 [北京], 红代会北京建筑工业学院八一战斗团, 1967 September 25 (Box-folder 1: 14)
  - Ba yi zhan bao 八一战报 [北京], 北京建筑工业学院八一战报编辑部, 北京地质学院东方红报编辑部, 1967 August 3, October 5 (Box-folder 1: 15)
  - Bai wan gong nong 百万工农 [保定], 河北保定工代会筹委会, 河北保定铁路工代会, 河北保定市贫代会, 1968 January 9-10 (Box-folder 1: 16)
  - Bai wan xiong shi 百万雄师 [保定], 河北省保定大中学校革命造反派联合指挥部, 1967 July 15 (Box-folder 1: 17)
  - Bao ding gong ren 保定工人 [保定], 河北保定工人总部保定工人编辑部, 1968 May 20 (Box-folder 1: 18)
  - Bao ding hong wei bing 保定红卫兵 保定, 保定市大中学校红卫兵代表大会, 1967 August 16, November 22 (Box-folder 1: 19)
  - Bei da xin xiao kan 北大新校刊 [北京, 北京大学], 1966 August 15 (Box-folder 1: 20)
  - Bei gong dong fang hong 北工东方红 [北京], 北京工业学院革命委员会筹办小组, 首都红代会北京工业学院东方红公社北工东方红编辑部, 1968 May 30, July (Box-folder 1: 21)
  - Bei gong hong qi 北工红旗 [北京], 首都红代会北京工业学院红旗公社, 1967 August, December (Box-folder 1: 22)
  - Bei guang 北光 [N.p.], 工代会775厂革委会宣传组, 1967 August 18 (Box-folder 1: 23)
  - Bei jing gong ren 北京工人 [北京], 北京市革命职工代表会议常设委员会, 1967 April-October (Box-folder 1: 24)
  - Bei jing gong she 北京公社 [北京], 首都三司中央财政金融学院红卫兵, 北京公社八.八战斗队, 1967 February-June (Box-folder 1: 25)
  - Bei jing ping lun 北京评论 [北京], 北京评论社, 1967 February 23 (Box-folder 1: 26)
  - Bei jing ri bao 北京日报 [北京, 北京日报社], 1967 January-April (Box-folder 1: 27)
  - Bei jing ri bao 北京日报 [北京], 北京市革命委员会机关报, 1967 May 1 and 17 (Box-folder 1: 28)
  - Bei jing wen yi zhan bao 北京文艺战报 北京, 北京市直属文化艺术系统联合斗批大会筹办处, 1967 July 13 (Box-folder 1: 29)
  - Bei jing xin wen yi 北京新文艺 [北京], 北京市文联革命造反派联络站, 北京市彻底摧毁反革命修正主义文艺黑线联络站, 1967 May-June (Box-folder 1: 30)
  - Bei jing yuan xiao hong wei bing 北京院校红卫兵 北京, 院校红卫兵联络总站, 1967 February 22 (Box-folder 1: 31)
  - Bei lin dong fang hong 北林东方红 [北京], 红代会北京林学院北林东方红编辑部, 1967 April 22 (Box-folder 1: 32)
  - Bei you dong fang hong 北邮东方红 [北京], 红代会北京邮电学院东方红公社, 1967 March-June (Box-folder 1: 33)
  - Bing tuan zhan bao 兵团战报 北京, 毛泽东思想红卫兵首都兵团政治部, 宣传部, 1966 November-December; 1967 January-July (Box-folder 1: 34)
  - Bing tuan zhan bao 兵团战报 [成都], 成都工人革命造反兵团动态组, 1967 May 30 (Box-folder 1: 35)
  - Bing tuan zhan shi bao 兵团战士报 [沈阳], 中国人民解放军沈阳军区黑龙江生产建设兵团政治部, 1969 June (Box-folder 1: 36)
  - Bo er ta la bao 博尔塔拉报 [博尔塔拉蒙古自治州], 1966 April 2-June 29, July 3-September 30 (Box-folder 2: 1-2)
  - Cai mao hong qi 财贸红旗 北京, 全国财贸系统革命造反联络委员会, 1967 February (Box-folder 2: 3)
  - Cai mao jian bing 财贸尖兵 [北京], 北京财贸职工革命造反尖兵总部宣传部, 1968 March (Box-folder 2: 4)
  - Cai mao zhao bao 财贸战报 [上海], 上海财贸系统革命造反委员会, 1967 May 15 and 21 (Box-folder 2: 5)
  - Chang ban lian si 长办联司 [N.p.], 捍卫毛泽东思想长江流域规划办公室革命造反联合司令部宣传部, 1967 September 18 (Box-folder 2: 6)
  - Chang chun gong she 长春公社 [长春], 长春公社报编辑部, 1967 July-September; 1968 May-June (Box-folder 2: 7)
  - Chang chun hong wei bing 长春红卫兵 [长春], 红色造反者长春市红卫兵总部 (二总部), 1967 September 15-17; 1968 June 16 (Box-folder 2: 8)
  - Chang cheng 长城 [北京], 毛泽东思想哲学社会科学部, 红卫兵总队, 六一公社, 718连总, 红色造反者, 长城编辑部, 1967 December 3; 1968 January-May (Box-folder 2: 9)
  - Chang ying 长缨 [N.p.], 东北局机关红色革命造反团长缨编辑部, 1967 July 10 (Box-folder 2: 10)
  - Chang zheng 长征 北京, 首都红代会北石北京公社, 重庆反到底革命派, 首都赴万专区联合调查团, 1967 July 10 (Box-folder 2: 11)
  - Chang zheng zhan bao 长征战报 [天津], 天津市小百花剧团革命造反联合总部, 1967 June 17, September (Box-folder 2: 12)
  - Cheng jian zhan bao 城建战报 [北京], 北京市城建系统革命造反联络总部, 1967 March 15, June 27, October 5 (Box-folder 2: 12)
  - Chi wei jun 赤卫军 [上海], 赤卫军上海市大专院校革命委员会赤革会, 1967 May 15, June 1 (Box-folder 2: 13)
  - Chong feng hao 冲锋号 [N.p.], 株洲市机关革联总部, 株洲市文, 体, 新闻革联站, 1967 June 30 (Box-folder 2: 14)
  - Chong feng hao 冲锋号 [N.p.], 中国人民大学红卫兵驻宁联络站, 1967 February 18 (Box-folder 2: 15)
  - Chun lei 春雷 北京, 首都八一学校毛泽东思想革命造反联合总部, 1967 March-August (Box-folder 2: 16)
  - Ci du hong wei bing 瓷都红卫兵 [景德镇], 景德镇市大中学校红卫兵总指挥部, 1968 January 15 (Box-folder 2: 17)
  - Cui jiu zhan bao 摧旧战报 [北京], 彻底摧毁旧北京市委战斗兵团摧旧战报编辑部, 1967 May 17-25 (Box-folder 2: 18)
  - Cui zi zhan bao 摧资战报 [北京], 首都工代会无产阶级革命派揪斗刘少奇, 王光美联络站, 首都红代会政法公社红旗兵, 红涛, 看今朝联合反修纵队, 1967 October (Box-folder 2: 19)
  - Da dao Li jing quan 打倒李井泉 [重庆], 重庆大学红卫兵团8.15 战报编辑部, 八.一五战斗团424 部队, 1967 July (Box-folder 2: 20)
  - Da dao Tao zhu 打倒陶铸 [西安], 西安矿业学院矿院新声, 广播台编辑部, 1969 September 15 (Box-folder 2: 21)
  - Da han da jiao 大喊大叫 [北京], 首都中等学校红卫兵革命造反总勤务部宣传部, 1967 February-March (Box-folder 2: 22)
  - Da jun bao 大军报 [柳州], 广西四. 二二柳州革命造反大军, 1968 June 29 (Box-folder 2: 23)
  - Da pi pan bao 大批判报 [北京], 首都革命大批判联络站, 1967 August 5 (Box-folder 2: 24)
  - Da qing gong she 大庆公社 [北京], 红代会北京石油学院大庆公社编辑部, 1967 April-May (Box-folder 2: 25)
  - Di yi qi che zhi zao chang 第一汽车制造厂 [N.p.], 第一汽车制造厂革命造反总指挥部, 吉林工业大学红色造反大军, 1968 March 18 (Box-folder 2: 26)
  - Di yuan zhan bao 地院战报 [长春], 长春公社长春地质学院毛泽东思想战斗兵团, 1968 June 9 (Box-folder 2: 27)
  - Dian ying feng lei 电影风雷 [北京], 首都批判毒草电影联络站, 1967 June 1-8 (Box-folder 2: 28)
  - Dian ying ge ming 电影革命 [北京], 电影革命联络委员会八一电影制片厂革命造反总部, 1967 May-October (Box-folder 2: 29)
  - Dian ying hong bing 电影红兵 [北京], 北京电影学院井冈山公社, 1967 May 15 and 29 (Box-folder 2: 30)
  - Dian ying pi pan 电影批判 [北京], 首都工代会, 农代会, 大, 中院校红代会砸三旧批判毒草影片战斗组, 1967 April-June (Box-folder 2: 31)
  - Dian ying pi pan 电影批判 [天津], 天津市工农兵砸三旧批判毒草影片联络站, 1967 August (Box-folder 2: 32)
  - Dian ying zhan bao 电影战报 北京, 首都电影界革命派联合委员会电影战报编辑部, 1967 May, September (Box-folder 2: 33)
  - Dong cheng feng bao 东城风暴 [北京], 北京市革命职工代表会议常设委员会东城分会, 1967 December 7; 1970 January 7 (Box-folder 3: 1)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [北京], 工代会首钢职工东方红革命造反联合会, 1967 June 10 (Box-folder 3: 2)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [北京], 红代会北京第二医学院东方红编辑部, 1967 September 8 (Box-folder 3: 3)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [北京], 红代会北京钢铁学校东方红, 1967 July 8, September 14, December 4 (Box-folder 3: 4)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [北京], 红代会北京工业大学东方红公社东方红报编辑部, 1967 January-December (Box-folder 3: 5)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [北京], 红代会中国科学技术大学东方红编辑部, 1967 May 23, August-September (Box-folder 3: 6)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [北京], 京棉三厂东方红编辑部, 1967 March 6 (Box-folder 3: 7)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [北京], 师院东方红公社, 1967 May (Box-folder 3: 8)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [北京], 首都大专院校红卫兵总部, 1966 October-December; 1967 January-May (Box-folder 3: 9)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [北京], 首都红代会北京机械学院东方红公社, 1967 April 7, July 5, August 13 (Box-folder 3: 10)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [北京], 首都红代会北京矿业学院东方红, 1967 May, November (Box-folder 3: 11)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [北京], 中国科学院综合考察委员会东方红战斗团, 1967 January 30 (Box-folder 3: 12)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [杭州], 杭州大学东方红兵团东方红编辑部, 1967 May-June (Box-folder 3: 13)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [天津], 天津大专院校红代会河北财经学院东方红公社赴保调查组, 1967 May-June (Box-folder 3: 14)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [天津], 天津东方红歌舞团东方红公社, 1967 May (Box-folder 3: 15)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [武汉], 武汉地区红卫兵第三司令部东方红编辑部, 1967 April 17 (Box-folder 3: 16)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [N.p.], 广西4.22革命行动指挥部4.22战报编辑部, 首都红代会北京矿业学院东方红东方红报编辑部, 1967 August 10 (Box-folder 3: 17)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [N.p.], 河南医学院革命委员会, 1968 July 16 (Box-folder 3: 18)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [N.p.], 红三司武汉测绘学院东方红总部首届红代会, 1967 April 22 (Box-folder 3: 19)
  - Dong fang hong 东方红 [N.p.], 煤炭科学研究院革命造反联合总部东方红报编辑部, 北京矿业学院东方红报编辑部, 煤炭工业部干部学校抗大通讯编辑部, 1967 September 3 (Box-folder 3: 20)
  - Dong fang hong bao 东方红报 [北京], 北京地质学院东方红报编辑部, 1967 February-September (Box-folder 3: 21)
  - Dong fang hong zhan bao 东方红战报 [北京], 红代会北京农业机械化学院东方红公社, 1967 February 25, March 16, June 15 (Box-folder 3: 22)
  - Dong fang hong zhan bao 东方红战报 [南京], 红卫兵南京工学院东方红总部, 南京工学院东方红战斗公社, 1967 January-November; 1968 March-April (Box-folder 3: 23)
  - Dong fang hong zhan bao 东方红战报 扬州, 东方红农业大学东方红公社, 东方红农业大学革命委员会政治部, 1967 January-December; 1968 January-June (Box-folder 3: 24)
  - Dong feng 东风 [北京], 首都中学红代会东风编辑部, 1967 September 23 (Box-folder 3: 25)
  - Dong feng bao 东风报 [北京], 首都中学红卫兵司令部, 1967 January 26, February 8 (Box-folder 3: 26)
  - Dong feng bao 东风报 [北京], 首钢职工革命大联合委员会, 1967 October (Box-folder 3: 27)
  - Dong feng zhan bao 东风战报 [北京], 东风战斗兵团总联络站东风战报编委会, 1967 February 16, March 12 (Box-folder 3: 28)
  - Dong gong hong qi 东工红旗 [N.p.], 东北工学院红旗红卫兵, 造反团东工红旗编辑部, 1967 July 29; 1968 June 30 (Box-folder 3: 29)
  - Dong tai bao 动态报 [北京], 中国科学院 (京区) 革命造反派联合夺权委员会动态组, 1967 May 30 (Box-folder 3: 30)
  - Dou Luo zhan bao 斗罗战报 [N.p.], 中国人民解放军革命造反派斗罗大会筹备处, 1967 June 28 (Box-folder 3: 31)
  - Dou pi gai tong xun 斗批改通讯 北京, 高教部, 教育部革命派联合委员会筹委会, 1967 March 30 (Box-folder 3: 32)
  - Dou Tao zhan bao 斗陶战报 [北京], 斗争陶铸筹备处, 1967 July 29 (Box-folder 3: 33)
  - Dou Tao zhan bao 斗陶战报 桂林, 广西革命大学斗争陶铸联络站, 1968 July 29, August 17 (Box-folder 3: 34)
  - Dui wai wen hua zhan bao 对外文化战报 北京, 批判对外黑文化联络站, 1967 July-September (Box-folder 3: 35)
  - Er Chen shi jian 二陈事件 [北京], 北京工业大学革命委员会二陈事件专案组, 1967 December (Box-folder 4: 1)
  - Er qi feng bao 二七风暴 北京, 河南二七风暴编辑部, 1967 August 28 (Box-folder 4: 2)
  - Er qi gong ren bao 二七工人报 [郑州], 郑州地区工代会, 1968 July 6 (Box-folder 4: 3)
  - Er qi gong she bao 二七公社报 [N.p.], 河南二七公社, 1967 October 21; 1968 January 20, May 4, July (Box-folder 4: 4)
  - Er qi kuai bao 二七快报 [N.p.], 河南二.七公社宣传站, 1967 May 31 (Box-folder 4: 5)
  - Er qi zhan bao 二七战报 北京, 河南二七公社二七战报编辑部, 1967 June, August (Box-folder 4: 6)
  - Fan fu pi 反复辟 [西安], 西安地区926专案联合调查团, 1967 (Box-folder 4: 7)
  - Fan fu pi 反复辟 [N.p.], 河北省直保定地区反复辟联络站, 1967 August 9 (Box-folder 4: 8)
  - Fang yuan hong qi 纺院红旗 [N.p.], 红代会河北纺织工学院八一八红旗纺院红旗编辑部, 1967 May (Box-folder 4: 9)
  - Fang zhi zhan xun 纺织战讯 [上海], 上海纺织工业机关革命造反委员会, 1967 April 24, May 5 (Box-folder 4: 10)
  - Fei ming di 飞鸣镝 [N.p.], 七机部新九一五革命造反总部宣传组, 1967 February-March, May 20 (Box-folder 4: 11)
  - Feng lei 风雷 北京, 首都出版界革命造反总部, 1967 April-June, September-October (Box-folder 4: 12)
  - Fei lei ji 风雷激 [N.p.], 建工部革命造反总部风雷激编辑组, 1967 May 9, June 6, September 25 (Box-folder 4: 13)
  - Fu hu zhan bao 伏虎战报 [N.p.], 河北日报险峰兵团, 飞跃兵团, 1967 August 10-14 (Box-folder 4: 14)
  - Fu jian ge ming zao fan bao 福建革命造反报 [北京], 福建革命造反委员会赴京控告团, 北京工业大学革命委员会, 首都红代会北工大 东方红公社, 1967 August 23 (Box-folder 4: 15)
  - Fu ke nao ge ming 复课闹革命 [上海], 上海市中等学校教工革命造反委员会教革会, 1967 March 17 (Box-folder 4: 16)
  - Gang cheng zhan bao 钢城战报 [N.p.], 黄石工代会钢城战报编辑部, 1968 July 6 (Box-folder 4: 17)
  - Gang jiu yi san 钢九一三 [N.p.], 武汉地区毛泽东思想九一三战斗兵团, 1967 August 3 (Box-folder 4: 18)
  - Ge lian zhan bao 革联战报 [北京], 首都红卫兵革命造反委员会(红革会), 1967 February 7 (Box-folder 4: 19)
  - Ge lian zhan bao 革联战报 [N.p.], 河南二七公社河南日报社革联, 1968 June (Box-folder 4: 20)
  - Ge ming chuan lian 革命串联 [北京], 北京建筑工业学院革命串联编辑部, 1967 August-October (Box-folder 4: 21)
  - Ge ming chuan lian bao 革命串连报 [北京], 新北大革命串连报编辑部, 1966 December 5; 1967 January-February (Box-folder 4: 22)
  - Ge ming feng lei 革命风雷 [北京], 北京电影学院井冈山公社, 1967 April 15 (Box-folder 4: 23)
  - Ge ming gong ren bao 革命工人报 [北京], 首都职工革命造反总部, 1967 October 17 (Box-folder 4: 24)
  - Ge ming gong ren bao 革命工人报 [南京], 江苏南京地区工人革命大联合委员会, 1967 January-February (Box-folder 4: 25)
  - Ge ming lou 革命楼 [上海], 上海戏剧学院革命楼毛泽东主义红卫兵政治宣传部, 1968 March 28, May 1, June 5 (Box-folder 4: 26)
  - Ge ming qiao bao 革命侨报 [N.p.], 中侨委革命造反总指挥部, 1967 April 9, June 3, August 20 (Box-folder 4: 28)
  - Ge ming wen yi zhan bao 革命文艺战报 [北京], 首都革命文艺造反总部, 1967 March-May (Box-folder 4: 29)
  - Ge ming zao fan 革命造反 [北京], 中国科学院京区革命造反派联合夺权委员会, 1967 February-August; 1968 May 4; 1970 July-December (Box-folder 4: 30)
  - Ge ming zao fan bao 革命造反报 [保定], 保定革命造反报编辑部, 1967 August-September (Box-folder 4: 31)
  - Ge ming zao fan bao 革命造反报 北京, 中国科学院革命造反报编委员会, 1967 January 9 (Box-folder 4: 32)
  - Ge ming zao fan bao 革命造反报 (专刊) [杭州], 浙江大学革命造反报编辑部, 1967 May 16 (Box-folder 4: 33)
  - Ge ming zao fan bao 革命造反报 [马鞍山], 马鞍山革命造反派联合总指挥部, 1967 February-April (Box-folder 4: 34)
  - Ge ming zao fan bao 革命造反报 [上海], 红卫兵上海第三司令部, 1967 May 16 (Box-folder 4: 35)
  - Ge ming zao fan bao 革命造反报 [苏州], 苏州市红卫兵革命造反总司令部, 1967 March (Box-folder 4: 36)
  - Ge ming zao fan bao 革命造反报 [天津], 天津卫生系统无产阶级革命造反总部, 天津工矿企业无产阶级革命造反总部, 1967 March 16, May 26, August (Box-folder 4: 37)
  - Ge ming zao fan bao 革命造反报 [N.p.], 衡水革命造反报临时编辑组, 1967 July 13 (Box-folder 4: 38)
  - Ge ming zhi gong bao 革命职工报 天津, 天津市革命职工代表会议常务委员会, 1968 July (Box-folder 4: 39)
  - Gong an lian zong 公安联总 [N.p.], 长春公安联总编辑部, 北航红旗编辑部, 北京矿院东方红编辑部, 1967 August 30 (Box-folder 4: 40)
  - Gong jiao zhan bao 工交战报 [北京], 首都斗争反革命修正主义分子薄一波筹备处, 1967 June-September (Box-folder 4: 41)
  - Gong jiao zhan bao 工交战报 [太原], 太原革命造反司令部工交军团, 1967 December 7 (Box-folder 4: 42)
  - Gong jiao zhan bao 工交战报 [天津], 天津工交战报社, 1967 June 5, September 1 (Box-folder 4: 43)
  - Gong kuang zha bao 工矿战报 [天津], 天津工矿企业造反总部工矿战报编辑部, 1967 October (Box-folder 4: 44)
  - Gong nong bing dian ying 工农兵电影 [北京], 工农兵批判毒草影片联络站, 1967 April-July (Box-folder 4: 45)
  - Gong nong zhan bao 工农战报 [天津], 天津市工农毛泽东思想宣传队驻南开大学指挥部, 1968 October 25 (Box-folder 4: 46)
  - Gong ren ri bao 工人日报 北京, [工人日报社], 1967 January 17 (Box-folder 4: 47)
  - Gong ren zao fan bao 工人造反报 [上海], 上海工人革命造反总司令部, 1967 May 19 (Box-folder 4: 48)
  - Gong ren zhan bao 工人战报 [N.p.], 内蒙古东方红工人革命造反总司令部, 1967 June 29 (Box-folder 4: 49)
  - Gong zong si zhan bao 工总司战报 哈尔滨, 哈尔滨工人红色造反者总司令部, 1967 October 27 (Box-folder 4: 50)
  - Guang ming zhan bao 光明战报 [北京], 光明日报革命造反总部, 1967 August-December; 1968 January-April (Box-folder 4: 51)
  - Ha er bin lie huo 哈尔滨烈火 [哈尔滨], 哈尔滨工人红色造反者总司令部, 哈尔滨大专院校红色造反团造反到底总部, 哈一机红色造反团, 1967 (Box-folder 5: 1)
  - Hai he ping lun 海河评论 [天津], 天津市一机筹委河海评论编辑部, 1967 October 23, November (Box-folder 5: 2)
  - He bei hong wei bing 河北红卫兵 [保定], 河北保定大中学校红卫兵代表大会, 1967 August 1 (Box-folder 5: 3)
  - He bei ri bao 河北日报 保定, [河北日报社], 1967 January (Box-folder 5: 4)
  - He nan er qi bao 河南二七报 北京, 河南二七公社河南二七报编辑部, 1967 June 5, October 5, November 5 (Box-folder 5: 5)
  - Hong an zhan bao 红安战报 安源, 萍矿无产阶级革命造反派安源矿司令部, 江西师范学院井冈山兵团安批刘战斗队, 1967 May 16 (Box-folder 5: 6)
  - Hong bei ying 红北影 北京, 北京电影制片厂革筹会红北影编辑部, 1967 June-August (Box-folder 5: 7)
  - Hong deng bao 红灯报 [北京], 红代会北京电影学院东方红, 毛泽东共产主义公社联合委员会, 1967 May 9 (Box-folder 5: 8)
  - Hong er qi 红二七 [北京], 首都工代会铁路系统大联合筹备小组宣传组, 1967 May 1 (Box-folder 5: 9)
  - Hong fan jun 红反军 北京, 首都大专院校红代会北京商学院红反军编辑部, 1967 May-June (Box-folder 5: 10)
  - Hong fan zhan bao 红反战报 [北京], 北京轻工业学院红色造反委员会, 井冈山战斗兵团联合总部, 1967 March 29 (Box-folder 5: 11)
  - Hong feng 红锋 天津, 红锋报社, 1966 November 15; 1967 March 15 (Box-folder 5: 12)
  - Hong he da 红河大 [N.p.], 河北大学革命委员会, 1968 July 12 (Box-folder 5: 13)
  - Hong hong ping lun 红红评论 [上海], 大连毛泽东主义红卫兵驻沪联络站, 1967 February 15 (Box-folder 5: 14)
  - Hong jiao bing 红教兵 [北京], 北京市小学革命教师联络总部崇文分部红教兵团, 1967 May 15 (Box-folder 5: 15)
  - Hong jiao gong 红教工 [北京], 首都大专院校红教工革命造反联络委员会, 1966 December 28; 1967 January-February (Box-folder 5: 16)
  - Hong jun bao 红军报 [N.p.], 二总部吉林工业大学红色造反大军红军报编辑部, 1967 August-October (Box-folder 5: 17)
  - Hong jun gong 红军工 [哈尔滨], 哈尔滨军事工程学院红色造反团, 1967 October-November (Box-folder 5: 18)
  - Hong jun zhan bao 红军战报 [北京], 首都红军兵团宣传部, 1967 March 8 (Box-folder 5: 19)
  - Hong lian meng 红联盟 [N.p.] 山西省红色造反者联盟, 1967 September 21 (Box-folder 5: 20)
  - Hong lian zhan bao 红联战报 [北京], 北京电力公司革命委员会, 1967 December 26 (Box-folder 5: 21)
  - Hong pao bing 红炮兵 [N.p.], 河北大学毛泽东思想八.一八红卫兵红炮兵编辑部, 1967 May-June (Box-folder 5: 22)
  - Hong qi 红旗 [北京], 北京航空学院红旗战斗队, 1966 December 26; 1967 February-September; 1968 March-May (Box-folder 5: 23-24)
  - Hong qi 红旗 [北京], 红代会北京经济学院红旗公社红旗报编辑部, 1967 September-November (Box-folder 5: 25)
  - Hong qi 红旗 [广州], 广州批陶联委, 新一司美术学院, 红旗兵团, 1967 September 22 (Box-folder 5: 26)
  - Hong qi bao 红旗报 [北京], 首都红旗报社, 1967 January 22 (Box-folder 5: 27)
  - Hong qi bao 红旗报 [合肥], 合肥红旗报编辑部, 1967 December (Box-folder 5: 28)
  - Hong qi bao 红旗报 [N.p.], 三机部红旗总部, 1967 March 10 (Box-folder 5: 29)
  - Hong qi gong ren 红旗工人 [广州], 广州红旗工人革命造反总司令部红旗工人报编辑部, 1967 July 21 (Box-folder 5: 30)
  - Hong qi man juan 红旗漫捲 [N.p.], 第四机械工业部121革命造反兵团, 1967 July 29, September (Box-folder 5: 31)
  - Hong qi ping lun 红旗评论 [北京], 中国科学院革命造反团红旗联络站, 1967 January 25 (Box-folder 5: 32)
  - Hong qi zhan bao 红旗战报 [北京], 北京政法学院红卫兵, 1967 May-June (Box-folder 5: 33)
  - Hong qi zhan bao 红旗战报 [北京], 首都红代会河北北京师院红旗, 1967 September 13 (Box-folder 5: 34)
  - Hong qi zhan bao 红旗战报 天津, 天津文联红旗, 1967 April-December; 1968 January-March (Box-folder 5: 35)
  - Hong qi zhan bao 红旗战报 [N.p.], 第二轻工业部大联委红旗公社红旗战报编辑部, 北京矿业学院东方红东方红编辑部, 1967 October 9 (Box-folder 5: 36)
  - Hong se feng bao 红色风暴 [锦州], 锦州市无产阶级革命派联合委员会筹备委员会, 1968 January 6 (Box-folder 6: 1)
  - Hong se feng bao 红色风暴 [n.p.], 浙江省革命造反联合总指挥部红色风暴编辑部, 1967 January 20 (Box-folder 6: 2)
  - Hong se gong jiao 红色工交 [N.p.], 斗争薄一波余秋里批判谷牧联络委员会, 1967 April-June, September 20 (Box-folder 6: 3)
  - Hong se gong ren 红色工人 [保定], 河北保定工人革命造反总部, 1967 November-December (Box-folder 6: 4)
  - Hong se huo che tou 红色火车头 [徐州], 徐州铁路火车头红色造反团司令部, 1968 August 23 (Box-folder 6: 5)
  - Hong se lian luo bao 红色联络报 [N.p.], 全国革命造反红卫兵联络总部, 1967 (Box-folder 6: 6)
  - Hong se pi pan zhe 红色批判者 [北京], 首都批判资产阶级反动学术权威联络委员会, 1967 May-September (Box-folder 6: 7)
  - Hong se shu guang 红色曙光 [安源], 江西萍乡红色曙光编委会, 1967 February 26 (Box-folder 6: 8)
  - Hong se wen yi 红色文艺 [北京], 首都文艺界红色造反总部, 1967 May-July (Box-folder 6: 9)
  - Hong se xiao xi 红色消息 天津, 天津市三建公司革命委员会, 1967 October (Box-folder 6: 10)
  - Hong se xuan chuan 红色宣传 [天津], 天津市宣传系统无产阶级革命派联合委员会, 1967 August (Box-folder 6: 11)
  - Hong se xuan chuan bing 红色宣传兵 [北京], 首都出版系统革命造反委员会, 1967 April-May (Box-folder 6: 12)
  - Hong se yin mu 红色银幕 [北京], 北京市电影发行放映公司, 1967 June 24, August-December (Box-folder 6: 13)
  - Hong se zao fan bao 红色造反报 [北京], 北京石油学院大庆公社宣传组, 1967 February 16 (Box-folder 6: 14)
  - Hong se zao fan bao 红色造反报 [北京], 首都职工红色造反总联络站宣传部, 1967 January-March (Box-folder 6: 15)
  - Hong se zao fan bao 红色造反报 北京, 中国人民解放军第二军医大学红色造反报编辑室, 1967 February 14 (Box-folder 6: 16)
  - Hong se zao fan bao 红色造反报 [北京], 中央戏剧学院红色造反团, 1967 February (Box-folder 6: 17)
  - Hong se zao fan bao 红色造反报 [清江市], 清江市无产阶级革命派大联合工人联合总站, 1967 March-December; 1968 January-October (Box-folder 6: 18)
  - Hong se zao fan bao 红色造反报 [N.p.], 空军技术学院红色造反纵队, 1967 February 5 (Box-folder 6: 19)
  - Hong se zao fan bao 红色造反报 [天津], 天津红色造反报编辑部, 1967 March (Box-folder 6: 20)
  - Hong se zao fan bao 红色造反报 [N.p.], 中国人民解放军后字二五二部队革命委员会红色造反总司令部, 1967 December 26 (Box-folder 6: 21)
  - Hong se zao fan tuan 红色造反团 保定, 保定大中学校红代会, 河北农业大学红色造反团红色造反团编辑部, 1967 June 29 (Box-folder 6: 22)
  - Hong se zao fan zhe 红色造反者 [N.p.], 鸡西市红色造反者, 1967 January 3 (Box-folder 6: 23)
  - Hong se zao fan zhe 红色造反者 [北京], 中国人民大学红旗, 1967 February 20 (Box-folder 6: 24)
  - Hong se zao fan zhe 红色造反者 [哈尔滨], 哈尔滨工程学院红色造反团 – 毛泽东思想红卫兵总部, 1966 October 8; 1967 June 29 (Box-folder 6: 25)
  - Hong se zhan bao 红色战报 [北京], 北京二七机车车辆工厂红色造反团, 1967 March 1 (Box-folder 6: 26)
  - Hong se zhi gong 红色职工 北京, 北京职工红色造反团, 首都政法兵团, 1967 January, March 2 (Box-folder 6: 27)
  - Hong Tai yuan 红太原 [太原], 红太原报社, 1967 May-July (Box-folder 6: 28)
  - Hong tie dao 红铁道 [大连], 大连铁道学院红色造反团, 1967 February 11 (Box-folder 6: 29)
  - Hong tie yuan 红铁院 兰州, 甘肃省大专院校红委会兰州铁道学院红司红铁院编辑部, 1967 July 18 (Box-folder 6: 30)
  - Hong wei bao 红卫报 [北京], 北京外国语学院, 1966 December 26; 1967 January-December (Box-folder 6: 31)
  - Hong wei bao 红卫报 [丹东], 毛泽东思想红卫兵丹东总部筹委会, 1966 December 3 (Box-folder 6: 32)
  - Hong wei bao 红卫报 [沈阳], 毛泽东思想红卫兵沈阳总部, 1967 May 4 (Box-folder 6: 33)
  - Hong wei bao 红卫报 [N.p.], 1967 August 16 (Box-folder 6: 34)
  - Hong wei bing 红卫兵 [北京], 首都大专院校红卫兵司令部政治部, 1966 October-December; 1967 January-February (Box-folder 6: 35)
  - Hong wei bing 红卫兵 [贵阳], 贵阳市大中学校毛泽东思想红卫兵司令部, 1967 January 28 (Box-folder 6: 36)
  - Hong wei bing 红卫兵 [天津], 天津东风大学革命造反红卫兵红卫兵编辑部, 南开大学八.一八红色造反团新南开编辑部, 1967 May 13 (Box-folder 6: 37)
  - Hong wei bing 红卫兵 [天津], 天津工学院红卫兵八.二五, 1967 June 13 (Box-folder 6: 38)
  - Hong wei bing bao 红卫兵报 北京, 红卫兵报编辑部, 1966 September-November (Box-folder 6: 39)
  - Hong wei bing bao 红卫兵报 [北京], 首都红卫兵纠察队西城分队指挥部, 1966 September 4 (Box-folder 6: 40)
  - Hong wei bing bao 红卫兵报 [北京], 首都中学红代会机关报红卫兵报编辑部, 1968 March-April (Box-folder 6: 41)
  - Hong wei bing bao 红卫兵报 [北京], 中国科学院红卫兵革命造反司令部红卫兵报编辑部, 1967 January 11, March 20, June- July (Box-folder 6: 42)
  - Hong wei bing bao 红卫兵报 成都, 成都电讯工程学院红旗战斗团, 红卫兵成电总勤务站, 1966 December (Box-folder 6: 43)
  - Hong wei bing bao 红卫兵报 (重庆专刊) 重庆, 首都大专院校红卫兵代表大会赴渝战斗兵团, 中国科学院红卫兵革命造反司令部赴渝调查组, 1967 June 22 (Box-folder 6: 44)
  - Hong wei bing bao 红卫兵报 桂林, 桂林市大中学校红卫兵总部, 1967 May 10 (Box-folder 6: 45)
  - Hong wei bing bao 红卫兵报 [南京],红卫兵南京大专院校司令部 (红二司), 1966 December 22; 1967 January-August (Box-folder 6: 46)
  - Hong wei bing zhan bao 红卫兵战报 [N.p.], 毛泽东主义红卫兵, 华南农学院野战团, 1967 January 20 (Box-folder 6: 47)
  - Hong wei bing zhi ge 红卫兵之歌 [北京], 红卫兵之歌编辑部, 1967 July 6 (Box-folder 6: 48)
  - Hong wei zhan bao 红卫战报 [北京], 首都红代会中国人民大学红卫兵, 红卫队, 东方红公社, 1967 April (Box-folder 6: 49)
  - Hong wei zhan bao 红卫战报 [北京], 外交学院革命造反兵团, 1967 March, May 22 (Box-folder 6: 50)
  - Hong wei zhan bao 红卫战报 [上海], 红卫兵上海市大专院校革命委员会, 红卫兵上海司令部, 1966 November 5; 1967 January 15, May 20 (Box-folder 6: 51)
  - Hong wu yi 红五一 [N.p.], 红五一反修军团, 1967 June 13 (Box-folder 6: 52)
  - Hong Xian you 红仙游 [仙游], 福建仙游革命造反总指挥部, 1968 June 30 (Box-folder 7: 1)
  - Hong xiao bing bao 红小兵报 南京, 红小兵报社, 1967 May 4 (Box-folder 7: 2)
  - Hong yan zhan bao 红岩战报 北京, 红岩战报社, 1967 April 23, June 5 (Box-folder 7: 3)
  - Hong ye yuan 红冶院 [西安], 西安冶金建筑学院革命委员会, 1967 September 2 (Box-folder 7: 4)